user: The day I went blind
was the scariest day of my life.
Nothing would ever be the same.
How would I do anything?
Reading, writing, even walking were things
I could no longer take for granted.
[footsteps]
I remember as a kid, I used to be able to
see clear views around my neighborhood.
[child shouts happily]
Over the years, things started to fade.
Letters, words, signs,
even big ones became blurry
and hard to read...
[birds chirping]
Till one day it was all gone.
[animal howling]
I was so scared.
I was suddenly seeing nothing,
even with my eyes wide open.
But then I learned that my smartphone
had all these amazing accessibility
features, like screen readers.
As I played with my phone
and explored different apps,
I noticed that some
were easier to use than others.
For example, in some apps, I could hear...
phone:
Unlabeled button, unlabeled button.
user:
But in others...
phone:
Play video button.
Close button.
Create button.
user: And now I know
I've got a better experience
when the app has
accessibility labels for buttons.
The labels enable me
to use the phone on my own.
I'm now able to do lots of things
that I never thought would be possible
when I first lost my sight.