[indistinct chatter, birds chirping,
car horn honking]
user: I really never thought
about how many sounds were around me...
until I started to lose my hearing.
Stuff like cars and kids...
Dogs barking...
[dog barks]
Phones ringing...
[cell phones ringing]
I guess I kind of took it for granted
that I'd always hear them,
even if they were only background noise.
But at some point, the sounds
just kind of started to dissolve away.
[static hissing]
And then it just became, like, noise.
For a while, that's all I heard--
just noise
without any specific sounds
that I could recognize.
Then one night I came across this movie,
and it had captions like...
"small dog is barking."
And I knew exactly what that sounded like.
Even though I couldn't actually hear
the barking,
I could remember it.
[dog barking]
That really made such a difference for me.
I felt like I could just sit back
and get lost in the movie.