[school bell rings]
user: No one thought I would get a PhD
because I couldn't read
until I was in high school.
[students chatting]
School was always tough for me
and I really struggled
to get through college.
But getting my PhD
was actually a breeze.
I know that sounds odd,
but I found this amazing counselor
who helped me figure out
that I had a learning disability.
I learned methods to make reading
easier for me.
For example, I highlighted text--
[highlighter scratching]
Which is still an option
while reading on my phone.
I appreciate it
when the writing is clear and concise
and broken up into small chunks.
It's easier for me to absorb.
My PhD is in English
so that I could teach others to write.
[pencil scratching]
Learning to better articulate
your thoughts is beneficial
in all kinds of writing,
from essays to poems,
even technical writing.
If an idea is clearly expressed,
it's not simply easier to understand
for people with learning disabilities.
It's easier for everyone who reads it.
[musical flourish]