[school bell rings]
user: Let me tell you about something
that happened to me in high school.
[students chatting]
Like most kids,
I had a vibrant social life,
you know, I was doing well
with my grades,
and I was even a, you know, an athlete
on the basketball team,
so things were going well.
[whistle blowing]
And then one day--
[horn blares]
[crash]
I was in a car crash.
[sirens wailing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
I had to spend a long time
in the hospital.
[sirens wailing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
My friends would try
to make me feel better,
but they had their own lives going on
outside of the hospital.
Here I was, confined to my bed.
[hospital equipment beeping]
What I did to escape
was I used my phone.
I, you know, would read books
or watch movies
or, you know, play with different apps.
[lasers firing]
But it wasn't always easy to do.
I didn't have full use of my hands.
You know, my--
my wrists weren't in perfect shape,
so my hands shook a little bit.
[tapping]
So I had trouble tapping certain spots
on the phone.
[frustrated tapping]
Smaller and larger touch targets
may sound insignificant,
but their size truly made a difference
during the year that I spent
in the hospital.
[upbeat music]